DVAITH NARAYANAN

figure glitchy.systems

advaith@glitchy.systems @advaithnarayan

Experienced DevOPs Engineer Specializing In Systems Programs And A Passionate Problem Solver

ABOUT

Hello there! I'm a tech enthusiast with a passion for learning and a curious mind that drives me to explore any topic that catches my interest. I have extensive experience in programming, with proficiency in Rust, Python, C/C++, JavaScript, Git & GitHub, HTML, CSS, Bash & Batch Scripting, and more languages,

EXPERTISE

- Cloud Enggineer
 - Azure
 - o GCP
 - AWS

- DevOps
- **Docker**
- Linux Systems Administration Project Management
- Rust & Python
- · Fusion360, Blender, Photoshop

EDUCATION

Muthoot Institute Of Techology and Science, Varikoli

Nov 2021 - Present

Pursuing Bachelor of Technology Computer Science (Minor in Mathematics)

Bhavans Vidya Mandir, Eroor (CBSE)

12th (Computer Science), 10th

July 2008 - Mar 2021

May 2022 - Present

WORK EXPERIENCE

GOOGLE CLOUD TECHNICAL TEAM

Muthoot Institute Of Techology and Science, Varikoli

- Deployments of college projects.
- Provided Technical Support for Deployment and Cloud Infrastructure Solutions.
- Production Deployment automation (Cloud build) on multiple college projects.
- Containerization and deployment of projects in a load-based scalable environments.

MEDIA CLUB TECHNICAL LEAD

Sept 2022 - Present

Muthoot Institute Of Techology and Science, Varikoli

- Deployment Lead for Collages Arts and Tech fests
- Was lead for the deployment and publishing of the websites for the MITS Media Club
- Manage the emails, storage solutions, permissions and security for the MITS Media Club

GDSC OPEN SOURCE LEAD

Sept 2022 - Present

Muthoot Institute Of Techology and Science, Varikoli

- Conducted a GDSC workshop introducing people to git and GitHub.
- Conducted an Introduction to Rust workshop at NIT Calicut during FOSSMeet'32.

CIDRIE SUMMER INTERN

May 2022 - Jul 2022

Muthoot Institute Of Techology and Science, Varikoli

- Worked on an Anti-Theft tracker project for Muthoot Finance.
- Created a server for debugging and testing the tracker devices.
- Worked on a shabbiness detection Machine Learning model, and helped with AI/ML projects there.
- Designed 3D models/animations for projects at CIDRIE

ACHIEVEMENTS & CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft Azure AZ-900

Mar 2023

Micrsoft

AWS Cloud Technical Essential

Mar 2022

Coursera

Learning Kubernetes

May 2023

LinkedIn Learning